Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1991 March-1991 April; DVD (Disc 68)
    - A different America, 1991 March 12 (Video 8)
    - A dose of tax reality, 1991 March 13 (Video 9)
    - Report card on children, 1991 March 14 (Video 10)
    - Freedom of information, 1991 March 15 (Video 11)
    - Unity of purpose, 1991 March 18 (Video 12)
    - There's never enough, 1991 March 19 (Video 13)
    - Spring is here, 1991 March 20 (Video 14)
    - Victims need help, 1991 March 21 (Video 15)
    - Story of two events, 1991 March 22 (Video 16)
    - Police chases deadly, 1991 March 25 (Video 17)
    - Another point of view - Ralph Cannon, re term limits, 1991 March 26 (Video 18)
    - Cheers for Runnin' Utes, 1991 March 27 (Video 19)
    - National Kidney Foundation, 1991 March 28 (Video 20)
    - Peace corps birthday, 1991 March 29 (Video 21)
    - ACLU off base, 1991 April 1 (Video 22)
    - Another point of view - Grant Mildenhall, re United Nations, 1991 April 2 (Video 23)
    - Eliminate W.A.C. tourney, 1991 April 3 (Video 24)
    - Technology highway needed, 1991 April 4 (Video 25)
    - Military doesn't change, 1991 April 5 (Video 26)
    - About planning vacation, 1991 April 8 (Video 27)
    - Court decision misread, 1991 April 9 (Video 28)
    - Celebrating the victory, 1991 April 10 (Video 29)
    - Road to Birmingham, 1991 April 11 (Video 30)
    - Ethics hearings fail, 1991 April 12 (Video 31)
    - Death and taxes, 1991 April 15 (Video 32)
    - Another point of view, Karl Swan, re taxes and tax load, 1991 April 16 (Video 33)
    - Ahead in Mideast, 1991 April 17 (Video 34)
    - Emma Eccles Jones, 1991 April 18 (Video 35)
    - Changing bank laws, 1991 April 19 (Video 36)
    - Don't take it anymore, 1991 April 22 (Video 37)
    - Careful of 900 numbers, 1991 April 23 (Video 38)
    - Professional Secretaries Day, 1991 April 24 (Video 39)
    - Organ Donor Week, 1991 April 25 (Video 40)
    - Everyone welcome here, 1991 April 26 (Video 41)
    - Cars and competition, 1991 April 29 (Video 42)
    - Hospital cost tradeoffs, 1991 April 30 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1991 May-1991 June; DVD (Disc 69)
    - Hold on to dear life, 1991 May 1 (Video 1)
    - Prison population alarming, 1991 May 2 (Video 2)
    - After a tough winter, 1991 May 3 (Video 3)
    - We need the water, 1991 May 6 (Video 4)
    - Another point of view - Leland Hogan, re telephone rate increase, 1991 May 7 (Video 5)
    - President's eudcation package, 1991 May 8 (Video 6)
    - Thanks, Steve Erickson, 1991 May 9 (Video 7)
    - Stuck in Mideast politics, 1991 May 10 (Video 8)
    - College is worth it, 1991 May 13 (Video 9)
    - Utah best run state, 1991 May 14 (Video 10)
    - Money for the arts, 1991 May 15 (Video 11)
    - Learning from children, 1991 May 16 (Video 12)
    - Forget term limits, 1991 May 17 (Video 13)
    - The Jazz are winners, 1991 May 20 (Video 14)
    - Taking care of children, 1991 May 21 (Video 15)
    - America - Japan week, 1991 May 22 (Video 16)
    - At graduation time, 1991 May 23 (Video 17)
    - Ethics by regulation, 1991 May 24 (Video 18)
    - Memorial Day, 1991 May 27 (Video 19)
    - Another point of view - Col. Frank Cox, re Steve Erickson, 1991 May 28 (Video 20)
    - Ethics reform needed, 1991 May 29 (Video 21)
    - System needs fixing, 1991 May 30 (Video 22)
    - Monkey wrench strategy, 1991 May 31 (Video 23)
    - Movement on gun control, 1991 June 3 (Video 24)
    - Storm drain fees, 1991 June 4 (Video 25)
    - Stop nuclear testing, 1991 June 5 (Video 26)
    - You can make a difference, 1991 June 6 (Video 27)
    - Money and progress, 1991 June 7 (Video 28)
    - Senator Garn decides, 1991 June 10 (Video 29)
    - Children at play, 1991 June 11 (Video 30)
    - Country restaurant tax, 1991 June 12 (Video 31)
    - Games with redistricting, 1991 June 13 (Video 32)
    - Freeways won't be free, 1991 June 14 (Video 33)
    - Time to regroup, 1991 June 17 (Video 34)
    - Politics and quotas, 1991 June 18 (Video 35)
    - Utah Jazz band, 1991 June 19 (Video 36)
    - Child safety tips, 1991 June 20 (Video 37)
    - Go for space station, 1991 June 21 (Video 38)
    - Don't glorify war, 1991 June 24 (Video 39)
    - Next for olympics, 1991 June 25 (Video 40)
    - Welcome, square dancers, 1991 June 26 (Video 41)
    - Aid to soviets, 1991 June 27 (Video 42)
    - Balance of nature, 1991 June 28 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1991 July-1991 August; DVD (Disc 70)
    - Thanks to Chase Peterson, 1991 July 1 (Video 1)
    - Summer fun time, 1991 July 2 (Video 2)
    - Reject "political correctness", 1991 July 3 (Video 3)
    - Fourth of July, 1991 July 4 (Video 4)
    - On becoming competitive, 1991 July 5 (Video 5)
    - Michael Landon's death, 1991 July 8 (Video 6)
    - Smart highways ahead, 1991 July 9 (Video 7)
    - Too many murders, 1991 July 10 (Video 8)
    - Child proof bottles, 1991 July 11 (Video 9)
    - Luxuries become necessities, 1991 July 12 (Video 10)
    - Welcome, county officials, 1991 July 15 (Video 11)
    - Needs of Utah's children, 1991 July 16 (Video 12)
    - Bill of rights, 1991 July 17 (Video 13)
    - Decade of "fixing", 1991 July 18 (Video 14)
    - California needs water, 1991 July 19 (Video 15)
    - Take pride in America, 1991 July 22 (Video 16)
    - Another point of view, Kelly Jarvis, re health care costs, 1991 July 23 (Video 17)
    - Pioneer Day, 1991 July 24 (Video 18)
    - Reconsider telephone order, 1991 July 25 (Video 19)
    - Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, 1991 July 26 (Video 20)
    - Property tax confusion, 1991 July 29 (Video 21)
    - Another point of view, Randall Doyle, re funding for olympics, 1991 July 30 (Video 22)
    - Bad news radio, 1991 July 31 (Video 23)
    - Limiting college enrollments, 1991 August 1 (Video 24)
    - Improve car safety, 1991 August 2 (Video 25)
    - Testing doctors for AIDS, 1991 August 5 (Video 26)
    - Peace talks in Mideast, 1991 August 6 (Video 27)
    - Understanding Utah drivers, 1991 August 7 (Video 28)
    - Steady tax load, 1991 August 8 (Video 29)
    - Meals on wheels, 1991 August 9 (Video 30)
    - Hogle Zoo birthday, 1991 August 12 (Video 31)
    - Another point of view - Herm Olsen, re regulating utilities, 1991 August 13 (Video 32)
    - Proper grazing fees, 1991 August 14 (Video 33)
    - Earthquakes and schools, 1991 August 15 (Video 34)
    - Vagrants and weirdos, 1991 August 16 (Video 35)
    - Focus on education, 1991 August 19 (Video 36)
    - Abusing social security, 1991 August 20 (Video 37)
    - Who are the homeless?, 1991 August 21 (Video 38)
    - The first amendment, 1991 August 22 (Video 39)
    - Drugs in the workplace, 1991 August 23 (Video 40)
    - Salt Palace changes, 1991 August 26 (Video 41)
    - Another point of view - Joe Ingles re telephone rate increase, 1991 August 27 (Video 42)
    - Too many hungry, 1991 August 28 (Video 43)
    - Teaching and learning, 1991 August 29 (Video 44)
    - New under the sun, 1991 August 30 (Video 45)
  - KSL editorials, 1991 September-1991 October; DVD (Disc 71)
    - Labor Day, 1991 September 2 (Video 1)
    - Welcome, President Smith, 1991 September 3 (Video 2)
    - Changes in Russia, 1991 September 4 (Video 3)
    - State fair time, 1991 September 5 (Video 4)
    - School tests useless, 1991 September 6 (Video 5)
    - Gang violence escalates, 1991 September 9 (Video 6)
    - Soviet empire collapse, 1991 September 10 (Video 7)
    - Hold on for dear life, 1991 September 11 (Video 8)
    - The seconed amendment, 1991 September 12 (Video 9)
    - Rich or poor?, 1991 September 13 (Video 10)
    - Please immunize children, 1991 September 16 (Video 11)
    - Salt Lake mayor's race, 1991 September 17 (Video 12)
    - C.U.P. on hold again, 1991 September 18 (Video 13)
    - Building code enforcement, 1991 September 19 (Video 14)
    - Utah drivers again, 1991 September 20 (Video 15)
    - Protecting the president, 1991 September 23 (Video 16)
    - Education must change, 1991 September 24 (Video 17)
    - The third amendment, 1991 September 25 (Video 18)
    - Promises to children, 1991 September 26 (Video 19)
    - Changing the Soviet economy, 1991 September 27 (Video 20)
    - Learn from the pain, 1991 September 30 (Video 21)
    - Caring in business, 1991 October 1 (Video 22)
    - Every four years, 1991 October 2 (Video 23)
    - The fourth amendment, 1991 October 3 (Video 24)
    - Too many desks, 1991 October 4 (Video 25)
    - Time to vote, 1991 October 7 (Video 26)
    - Education technology initiative, 1991 October 8 (Video 27)
    - Delta Center opens, 1991 October 9 (Video 28)
    - Helping others grow, 1991 October 10 (Video 29)
    - Eating out in America, 1991 October 11 (Video 30)
    - Education report card, 1991 October 14 (Video 31)
    - Health care costs, 1991 October 15 (Video 32)
    - Blame for the debt, 1991 October 16 (Video 33)
    - Gangs and the family, 1991 October 17 (Video 34)
    - Manufacturing continues to grow, 1991 October 18 (Video 35)
    - The thomas hearings, 1991 October 21 (Video 36)
    - Ballet West shines, 1991 October 22 (Video 37)
    - Lessons from hearings, 1991 October 23 (Video 38)
    - United Nations Day, 1991 October 24 (Video 39)
    - Support United Way, 1991 October 25 (Video 40)
    - Brush fire danger, 1991 October 28 (Video 41)
    - Mideast peace conference, 1991 October 29 (Video 42)
    - Education and critics, 1991 October 30 (Video 43)
    - The fifth amendment, 1991 October 31 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1991 November-1991 December; DVD (Disc 72)
    - More news is good news, 1991 November 1 (Video 1)
    - The importance of voting, 1991 November 4 (Video 2)
    - Goodbye, Fort Douglas, 1991 November 5 (Video 3)
    - Taxing Utah hospitals, 1991 November 6 (Video 4)
    - The sixth amendment, 1991 November 7 (Video 5)
    - Here we go, again, 1991 November 8 (Video 6)
    - Veterans Day, 1991 November 11 (Video 7)
    - Cost of S&L mess, 1991 November 12 (Video 8)
    - Lowell Bennion Center, 1991 November 13 (Video 9)
    - Map makers nightmare, 1991 November 14 (Video 10)
    - The seventh amendment, 1991 November 15 (Video 11)
    - Cable television threat, 1991 November 18 (Video 12)
    - Another point of view, Chris Allen, re taxes and hospitals, 1991 November 19 (Video 13)
    - Term limits defeated, 1991 November 20 (Video 14)
    - Candidate alienation danger, 1991 November 21 (Video 15)
    - Area banks strong, 1991 November 22 (Video 16)
    - Sorrow over Yugoslavia, 1991 November 25 (Video 17)
    - Penalty of bad policy, 1991 November 26 (Video 18)
    - Family day of thanks, 1991 November 27 (Video 19)
    - Spirit of gratitude, 1991 November 28 (Video 20)
    - The eighth amendment, 1991 November 29 (Video 21)
    - Hanukkah, 1991 December 2 (Video 22)
    - Credit card economy, 1991 December 3 (Video 23)
    - The ninth amendment, 1991 December 4 (Video 24)
    - Luxury often overlooked, 1991 December 5 (Video 25)
    - Pearl Harbor, 1991 December 6 (Video 26)
    - On stealing time (archive tape missing), 1991 December 9 (Video 27)
    - Quarters for Christmas (archive tape missing), 1991 December 10 (Video 28)
    - The tenth amendment (archive tape missing), 1991 December 11 (Video 29)
    - Candy and broccoli (archive tape missing), 1991 December 12 (Video 30)
    - "Designated driver" works (archive tape missing), 1991 December 13 (Video 31)
    - Smith rape trial (archive tape missing), 1991 December 16 (Video 32)
    - Another point of view, Verl McMillan, re term limits (archive tape missing), 1991 December 17 (Video 33)
    - Christmas for children (archive tape missing), 1991 December 18 (Video 34)
    - The enemy is dead (archive tape missing), 1991 December 19 (Video 35)
    - World as a unit (archive tape missing), 1991 December 20 (Video 36)
    - Will Rogers follies, 1991 December 23 (Video 37)
    - Christmas Eve, 1991 December 24 (Video 38)
    - Christmas Day, 1991 December 25 (Video 39)
    - Change nuclear policies, 1991 December 26 (Video 40)
    - Abortion legal fees, 1991 December 27 (Video 41)
    - Buy something new, 1991 December 30 (Video 42)
    - End of the year, 1991 December 31 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1992 January-1992 February; DVD (Disc 73)
    - A new year, 1992 January 1 (Video 1)
    - Right to education, 1992 January 2 (Video 2)
    - Protect gasoline bargain, 1992 January 3 (Video 3)
    - Welcome, Mayor Corradini, 1992 January 6 (Video 4)
    - Don't lower taxes, 1992 January 7 (Video 5)
    - Governor's budget proposal, 1992 January 8 (Video 6)
    - County commission and taxes, 1992 January 9 (Video 7)
    - Charity is not seasonal, 1992 January 10 (Video 8)
    - Utah legislative session, 1992 January 13 (Video 9)
    - Enough Japan bashing, 1992 January 14 (Video 10)
    - Logan arts center, 1992 January 15 (Video 11)
    - Caucuses evade law, 1992 January 16 (Video 12)
    - Truce in El Salvador, 1992 January 17 (Video 13)
    - Human Rights Day, 1992 January 20 (Video 14)
    - Thanks, Mr. 'C', 1992 January 21 (Video 15)
    - Paying for college, 1992 January 22 (Video 16)
    - School funds equalization, 1992 January 23 (Video 17)
    - Helmet law needed, 1992 January 24 (Video 18)
    - More science and math, 1992 January 27 (Video 19)
    - Gambling not wanted, 1992 January 28 (Video 20)
    - Hazardous waste fees, 1992 January 29 (Video 21)
    - Education strategic plan, 1992 January 30 (Video 22)
    - Expand education network, 1992 January 31 (Video 23)
    - Nintendo and the Mariners, 1992 February 3 (Video 24)
    - Preschool vision screening, 1992 February 4 (Video 25)
    - Check-off for homeless, 1992 February 5 (Video 26)
    - Thiokol honored by NASA, 1992 February 6 (Video 27)
    - Enjoy winter olympics, 1992 February 7 (Video 28)
    - Primary Children's radiothon, 1992 February 10 (Video 29)
    - Health care package, 1992 February 11 (Video 30)
    - Buy America? How?, 1992 February 12 (Video 31)
    - Jordanelle Dam Hearing, 1992 February 13 (Video 32)
    - Hunger and waste, 1992 February 14 (Video 33)
    - Presidents Day, 1992 February 17 (Video 34)
    - Utah growth curve, 1992 February 18 (Video 35)
    - Engineering week, 1992 February 19 (Video 36)
    - Tons of food, 1992 February 20 (Video 37)
    - Dubious ritual abuse, 1992 February 21 (Video 38)
    - Open meetings law, 1992 February 24 (Video 39)
    - Brigham Young statue, 1992 February 25 (Video 40)
    - Athletes with no home, 1992 February 26 (Video 41)
    - Helping troubled teens, 1992 February 27 (Video 42)
    - Better speech week, 1992 February 28 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1992 March-1992 April; DVD (Disc 74)
    - Motorcycle safety law (archive tape missing), 1992 March 2 (Video 1)
    - Centennial license plates (archive tape missing), 1992 March 3 (Video 2)
    - Grandchild safety bill (archive tape missing), 1992 March 4 (Video 3)
    - Lies and the press (archive tape missing), 1992 March 5 (Video 4)
    - Religion conquers communism (archive tape missing), 1992 March 6 (Video 5)
    - United Way tarnished (archive tape missing), 1992 March 9 (Video 6)
    - Sensible migration policy (archive tape missing), 1992 March 10 (Video 7)
    - People helping people (archive tape missing), 1992 March 11 (Video 8)
    - Infernal answering machines (archive tape missing), 1992 March 12 (Video 9)
    - Prayer and free speech (archive tape missing), 1992 March 13 (Video 10)
    - Year-around schools (archive tape missing), 1992 March 16 (Video 11)
    - Sports and TV (archive tape missing), 1992 March 17 (Video 12)
    - Prayer at public meetings (archive tape missing), 1992 March 18 (Video 13)
    - Generation gap widens (archive tape missing), 1992 March 19 (Video 14)
    - Electricity costs down (archive tape missing), 1992 March 20 (Video 15)
    - Guns and children (archive tape missing), 1992 March 23 (Video 16)
    - Utah opinion poll (archive tape missing), 1992 March 24 (Video 17)
    - Chistopher Columbus (archive tape missing), 1992 March 25 (Video 18)
    - Pioneer 10 at 20 (archive tape missing), 1992 March 26 (Video 19)
    - Help for Russia (archive tape missing), 1992 March 27 (Video 20)
    - Rubber check scandal (archive tape missing), 1992 March 30 (Video 21)
    - Information technology summit, 1992 March 31 (Video 22)
    - Kennecott invests in Utah (archive tape missing), 1992 April 1 (Video 23)
    - Property tax relief (archive tape missing), 1992 April 2 (Video 24)
    - Here's the bank story (archive tape missing), 1992 April 3 (Video 25)
    - LDS temple capstone (archive tape missing), 1992 April 6 (Video 26)
    - School success stories (archive tape missing), 1992 April 7 (Video 27)
    - Cuba will be next (archive tape missing), 1992 April 8 (Video 28)
    - Children win and lose, 1992 April 9 (Video 29)
    - Optimism of youth, 1992 April 10 (Video 30)
    - Dealing with panhandlers (archive tape missing), 1992 April 13 (Video 31)
    - Another point of view: Mike Sebastian, re guns and children (archive tape missing), 1992 April 14 (Video 32)
    - Education and problems (archive tape missing), 1992 April 15 (Video 33)
    - Aging brings progress (archive tape missing), 1992 April 16 (Video 34)
    - Priorities out of whack (archive tape missing), 1992 April 17 (Video 35)
    - Horse racing commission (archive tape missing), 1992 April 20 (Video 36)
    - Justice department confused (archive tape missing), 1992 April 21 (Video 37)
    - 24 hours for food (archive tape missing), 1992 April 22 (Video 38)
    - The money test (archive tape missing), 1992 April 23 (Video 39)
    - Discs and tapes (archive tape missing), 1992 April 24 (Video 40)
    - Rebuild Derks Field (archive tape missing), 1992 April 27 (Video 41)
    - The photo-cop ruckus (archive tape missing), 1992 April 28 (Video 42)
    - Another city plan (archive tape missing), 1992 April 29 (Video 43)
    - Summer planning time (archive tape missing), 1992 April 30 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1992 May-1992 June; DVD (Disc 75)
    - Out of touch, 1992 May 1 (Video 1)
    - Outrage!, 1992 May 4 (Video 2)
    - Midnight basketball works, 1992 May 5 (Video 3)
    - Stress higher education, 1992 May 6 (Video 4)
    - Maintain the reserve, 1992 May 7 (Video 5)
    - Gossip and the press, 1992 May 8 (Video 6)
    - Lessons from Los Angeles, 1992 May 11 (Video 7)
    - Party caucus worked, 1992 May 12 (Video 8)
    - Solving social problems, 1992 May 13 (Video 9)
    - Utah's economic power, 1992 May 14 (Video 10)
    - Promise of new technology, 1992 May 15 (Video 11)
    - Time to declassify, 1992 May 18 (Video 12)
    - Elections must change, 1992 May 19 (Video 13)
    - Downtown sports center, 1992 May 20 (Video 14)
    - Enterprise zone fallacy, 1992 May 21 (Video 15)
    - Human Rights Week, 1992 May 22 (Video 16)
    - Goodbye to arena, 1992 May 25 (Video 17)
    - Another point of view: Lynn Blake, re information technology, 1992 May 26 (Video 18)
    - Changes in Congress, 1992 May 27 (Video 19)
    - Student aid fiasco, 1992 May 28 (Video 20)
    - Children's miracle network, 1992 May 29 (Video 21)
    - Jazz focus attention, 1992 June 1 (Video 22)
    - Mayor's tough decisions, 1992 June 2 (Video 23)
    - Don't waste water, 1992 June 3 (Video 24)
    - Solving urban problems, 1992 June 4 (Video 25)
    - Discovery of the Americas, 1992 June 5 (Video 26)
    - Stop nuclear testing, 1992 June 8 (Video 27)
    - Honoring academic excellence, 1992 June 9 (Video 28)
    - Confidence in youth, 1992 June 10 (Video 29)
    - Please buckle up, 1992 June 11 (Video 30)
    - Reject welfare myths, 1992 June 12 (Video 31)
    - Expand Dimple Dell, 1992 June 15 (Video 32)
    - Landscape the freeway, 1992 June 16 (Video 33)
    - Restore battalion monument, 1992 June 17 (Video 34)
    - Red Butte Garden, 1992 June 18 (Video 35)
    - This strange election, 1992 June 19 (Video 36)
    - Earth summit worked, 1992 June 22 (Video 37)
    - Slaughter in Yugoslavia, 1992 June 23 (Video 38)
    - Summer water hazard, 1992 June 24 (Video 39)
    - Global warming nonsense, 1992 June 25 (Video 40)
    - Saturday morning news, 1992 June 26 (Video 41)
    - Get on with business, 1992 June 29 (Video 42)
    - Snails and somesense, 1992 June 30 (Video 43)
  - KSL editorials, 1992 July-1992 August; DVD (Disc 76)
    - Light rail surprises, 1992 July 1 (Video 1)
    - Enough Iran contra, 1992 July 2 (Video 2)
    - Fourth of July, 1992 July 3 (Video 3)
    - Locked cars and children, 1992 July 6 (Video 4)
    - Simple means complex, 1992 July 7 (Video 5)
    - Ozone threat increases, 1992 July 8 (Video 6)
    - Bears and campers, 1992 July 9 (Video 7)
    - Supreme court adrift?, 1992 July 10 (Video 8)
    - Speed skating oval, 1992 July 13 (Video 9)
    - Another point of view: Reed Swenson, re welfare abuse, 1992 July 14 (Video 10)
    - Utah symphony orchestra, 1992 July 15 (Video 11)
    - Economy in doldrums, 1992 July 16 (Video 12)
    - Don't misjudge tailhook, 1992 July 17 (Video 13)
    - Build the ball park, 1992 July 20 (Video 14)
    - Another point of view: Tim Provan, re bears and camping, 1992 July 21 (Video 15)
    - Must teach values, 1992 July 22 (Video 16)
    - On backs of states, 1992 July 23 (Video 17)
    - Pioneer Day, 1992 July 24 (Video 18)
    - Exit Ross Perot, 1992 July 27 (Video 19)
    - Police and cars, 1992 July 28 (Video 20)
    - Legislators should worry, 1992 July 29 (Video 21)
    - False tax saving, 1992 July 30 (Video 22)
    - Sense of crisis, 1992 July 31 (Video 23)
    - Nagoya project ends, 1992 August 3 (Video 24)
    - Another point of view: Jon Reston, re horse racing, 1992 August 4 (Video 25)
    - Preserve union fort, 1992 August 5 (Video 26)
    - Leisure and health, 1992 August 6 (Video 27)
    - Supreme court errs, 1992 August 7 (Video 28)
    - Learning about life, 1992 August 10 (Video 29)
    - The lotus project, 1992 August 11 (Video 30)
    - Raunchy lyrics drivel, 1992 August 12 (Video 31)
    - Learn from the British, 1992 August 13 (Video 32)
    - Nuclear energy reform, 1992 August 14 (Video 33)
    - Education and choice, 1992 August 17 (Video 34)
    - America's profanity insanity, 1992 August 18 (Video 35)
    - Hold the brass, 1992 August 19 (Video 36)
    - Youthful optimism shines, 1992 August 20 (Video 37)
    - The fourth dimension, 1992 August 21 (Video 38)
    - Minorities no longer, 1992 August 24 (Video 39)
    - No to horse racing, 1992 August 25 (Video 40)
    - Business helping education, 1992 August 26 (Video 41)
    - Children's television act, 1992 August 27 (Video 42)
    - Generosity in Vernal, 1992 August 28 (Video 43)
    - Columbus the bold, 1992 August 31 (Video 44)
  - KSL editorials, 1992 September-1992 October; DVD (Disc 77)
    - Boomers near fifty, 1992 September 1 (Video 1)
    - Utah science center, 1992 September 2 (Video 2)
    - Combine and focus, 1992 September 3 (Video 3)
    - Traffic and war, 1992 September 4 (Video 4)
    - Facing new challenges, 1992 September 7 (Video 5)
    - Another point of view: Leonard Arrington, re for union center, 1992 September 8 (Video 6)
    - Time for the fair, 1992 September 9 (Video 7)
    - Fund higher education, 1992 September 10 (Video 8)
    - Nursing home care, 1992 September 11 (Video 9)
    - Conference on families, 1992 September 14 (Video 10)
    - Deficit double talk, 1992 September 15 (Video 11)
    - Bring us together, 1992 September 16 (Video 12)
    - United Way campaign, 1992 September 17 (Video 13)
    - U.S. economy strong, 1992 September 18 (Video 14)
    - Year of disasters, 1992 September 21 (Video 15)
    - Equalize school funding, 1992 September 22 (Video 16)
    - Computers make a difference, 1992 September 23 (Video 17)
    - Future is bright, 1992 September 24 (Video 18)